上集回顾
Previously on Power...
我在你那儿发现的那些钱 汤米
All that money I found in your place, Tommy,
那可不是俱乐部的
that's not from the club.
我是个贩毒的
I'm a drug dealer.
这个地方检察官有一堆案子需要复审
This D.A. has a bunch of cases under judicial review.
所以你才得快点出来
That's why you're getting out fast.
什么时候?
When?
离伊莎贝尔远一点儿 诺马
Leave Isabel alone, Nomar.
貌似你在清理门户
Looks like you're cleaning house.
你在排除对手
Well, you're eliminating the competition.
我今天看见西蒙・斯特恩了
I saw Simon Stern today.
一切顺利
It went great.
维加斯 迈阿密
Vegas, Miami.
我喜欢迈阿密
Mm, I like Miami.
要是塔莎发现了是怎么回事
If Tasha ever found out,
她会毁了你的家庭和你经营的一切
she'd blow up your family and our whole game.
我给你弄了件小礼物
I got you a little something myself.
希望这个能博你一笑
I hope it makes you smile.
庆祝一下我的赎罪日
Celebrating my high holy day
然后就被这个婊子刺了一刀
and this puta sticks me.
袭击你的是个女的?
The hitter was a girl?
找到这个女的
We find this girl,
我们就能找到是谁在跟我们作对
we find out who's been hitting us.
等鲁伊斯和他身边的小头目谈生意的时候
Try to get yourself near Ruiz and his top guys
尽量靠他们近一些
when they're talking business.
特别是他们提到洛沃斯和散货商的时候
Especially if they mention Lobos or the distributor.
和鲁伊斯在一起的那个白痴是谁?
Who's the blanquito in there with Ruiz?
他就是给我们弄货的那个人 经销商
That's the guy who gets us the product, Distro.
你的大趴真是嗨过头了 T
Your party was over the top, "T."
是啊
Sure was.
我还在对付伏特加的宿醉
I'm still trying to work through that vodka hangover.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
再问一下 你老公给你了个什么来着?
What did your husband get you again?
他给她弄到了那个新的赛琳手提包
He got her that new Celine Tote,
跟卡内给吉姆买的那个一样
like Kanye got Kim,
然后还有个更刺激的东西
and then something a little more stimulating,
你懂的
if you know what I mean.
就是说你男人在床上拿出来了奢侈品?
So your man delivers in accessories and in bed?
该死的 塔莎 真是他妈的童话故事
Shit, Tasha, that's a goddamn fairy tale.
我也这么觉得
That's what I said.
这就是生活 姐儿们
It's just a life, y'all.
每人都一样 生活都是起起伏伏的
It's got its ups and downs like everybody else's.
我想知道他是怎么表白的
I want to know how he proposed.
我要记好笔记
I'm taking notes.
好吧 好了 记好了
All right, well, take notes,
因为我要开讲了
'cause I'm gonna tell the story.
这是我最爱的故事
It's my favorite story.
你知道 其实 她还只是个孩子呢
You know, basically, she was still a kid.
然后有一天 他们开车
And one day, they were driving
沿着新泽西的收费高速一路走
down the New Jersey turnpike.
不对 就是走的普通公路
No, it was the BQE.
好吧 随便吧
Okay, whatever.
然后警察拦住了他们
And then the cops pulled them over.
然后他就靠过来
So he leans in,
说 "嘿 我车里有把枪"
and he's like, "yo, I got a piece in the car."
为什么他会有一把枪?
Why did he have a gun?
防身嘛
For protection.
你也知道那些个兜帽仔都什么样
You know how the hood was.
那个就在车上的储物箱里
It was in the glove compartment.
警察走过来的时候
As the cop's walking up,
我把那个拿出来 藏在了我的钱包里
I take it out, put it in my purse.
警察搜了他的身
Cop searches him.
搜了搜车 一无所获
He searched the car, found nothing.
警察转身朝我走过来 瞅了瞅我
Cop walks up to me, eyeballs me.
我这辈子都没那么害怕过
I was never so scared in my life.
然后呢?
And then what happened?
他转身走开了
He just walks away.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
我现在也不明白
I still don't know why.
我们继续开走了 谁也没开口谈论那个
We drove away, didn't talk about it.
直到我们到家之前 我连哭一下都没有
I didn't even cry until we got home.
两天后 他给了我这枚戒指
Two days later, he gives me this ring.
你真是个冷血的婊子 T
You a stone cold bitch, "T."
生死极速啊
Ride or die.
你知道吗 他说他能信任我
Well, you know, he said he knew he could trust me.
他知道我会完全对他忠诚
He knew he had my complete loyalty.
然后我说只要他也对我如此
And I said as long as he gave me the same,
我们就会永远在一起
we'd be together forever.
我爱死这个故事了
I love that story.
每次我听你讲 都像是第一次听到一样兴奋
It's like the first time, every time I hear that story.
现在我们得想想怎么给你找到个男人
Now we got to figure out how to get you a man
一个房子还有一枚戒指
and a house and a ring,
因为你连为什么
'cause you didn't even understand
他车里有把枪都没搞明白
why he had a gun in the car.
我还是不明白为什么他需要那把枪
I still don't understand why he needed that gun.
多谢你能来这儿见我
Thanks for meeting me here.
我没法赶到上城区
I couldn't make it all the way uptown.
但是我还是想要见你
I still wanted to see you.
虽然我更喜欢在我公寓里
I prefer my apartment,
不过在这儿也有好处
but being here has certain benefits,
比如说客房服务
like room service.
老天 我真希望我能一整天都呆在这儿
God, I wish I could stay here all day.
我不想出去 去那个真实世界
I don't want to go out there, to the real world.
这一切 我们 才是真实的
This, us, is real.
我的女人
Woman.
你也这么觉得 对吧?
You feel that way, too, right?
嗯?
Hmm?
没关系
It's okay.
接吧
You can get it.
我再给她回
I'll call her back.
她是个什么样的人?
What's she like?
嗯 塔莎...
Well, Tasha is...
她不是你
Not you.
哦 太好了 幸好你在这儿
Oh, good, I'm glad you're here.
我能不能借借你的黑色皮夹克?
Do you mind if I borrow your black leather jacket?
什么?
What?
今天是周二 洗衣日
It's Tuesday, laundry day.
我是不是要先打个电话问问你?
Should I have called first?
现在吗何必呢
Why start now?
别穿着那个抽烟 行吗?
No smoking in it, okay?
我还在为我毛衣上的烟洞
I'm still angry about the burn hole
不爽着呢
that was in my sweater.
我三个月前戒烟了
I quit three months ago.
你去哪儿了?
Where you been?
算了 我大概能猜到
Never mind, I guess I know.
该死 在酒店里觉得激情多了 是吧?
Shit is so much hotter in hotels, right?
曼尼带我去过一次万豪酒店
Manny took me to the Marriott once,
还让我...
and let me...
我很高兴你跟格雷格
I'm just glad you finally found a way
之间又找回激情了
to get your fireworks with Greg.
我不再和格雷格一起了
I'm not with Greg anymore.
什么?
Y que?
你有了新欢
You got some new hot thing
却没告诉我?
you didn't tell me about?
很长一段时间 我都不知道那个算是什么
I didn't know what it was for a while,
所以我才什么也没说
so I didn't want to say anything.
他叫什么?
What's his name?
杰米・圣帕特里克
It's Jamie St. Patrick.
以前的老街坊?
From the old neighborhood?
我想我从来没放下过他
I guess I never really let him go.
我觉得是
I guess not,
不管爸爸把他
no matter how many times
赶出去多少次
papi chased him out of the house.
他就是个小混混 街角的小阿飞
He was a punk.A punk on the corner
给那帮黑帮放哨的
Playing lookout for those gangsters.
他变了
He's changed.
他已经不再是那样了
He's not like that anymore.
你已经陷进去了 是不是
You got it bad, don't you?
他是个不错的家伙 帕斯
He's a good guy, Paz.
你会发现的
You'll see.
我一定会的
I sure will.
一起吃晚饭怎么样?
How about dinner?
要是他跟你说的那么好
If he's as great as you say,
我觉得我是该见见我未来的妹夫了
it feels like I should re-meet my future cunado.
- 你会问他的 对吧? - 我会的
- You'll ask him, right? - I'll ask him.
我们不是在竞赛
We are not competition.
我们只是一对老朋友
We are only old friends.
你来向朋友求助不应该犹豫那么久
It should not take you so long to come to friend for help.
桑拿还带着枪
Guns in the sauna.
你们塞尔维亚人
You Serbians have an interesting way
表达友谊的方式可真有意思 弗拉基米尔
of defining friendship, Vladimir.
他们有点儿保卫过度了
They are overprotective.
我能说什么呢
What can I say?
现在 告诉我 我能帮你什么忙?
Now, tell me, how can I help?
我在找一个持枪歹徒...
I'm looking for a gun...
确切的说是一个雇佣的刀客
actually a knife for hire,
一个女的
a woman.
白人 西班牙人 还是黑人?
A white girl, Spanish, or a black?
肯定的说是拉丁裔的
Definitely Latin.
我跟一个来自新泽西的海地人有生意来往
I do business with a Haitian from New Jersey.
你一定要跟他聊聊
You must have conversation with him.
不过他比较...
But he is a little...
有意思
Interesting.
你说的是漂流(人名 外号)?
You talking about Drift?
我跟那个混账共事过
I got work with that motherfucker.
要是他知道什么跟这件事有关系的消息
If he knew something about this shit,
他应该跟我一起合作时候
he should've reached out.
就说出来了
When he and I worked together,
他知道要消除一个问题的时候要打给谁
he knew who to call to eliminate a problem.
要是她在那儿的话 他会知道她的
If she's out there, he'll know about her.
你听斯特恩说的?
You heard from Stern?
没有
No.
怎么了 你紧张了?
What, you getting nervous?
只是想知道这晚饭什么时候开始
Just want to know what time this dinner's gonna be.
像斯特恩那样的男人一年中有半年都在飞机上
Men like Stern are on a plane half the year.
我打赌他妻子压根都抓不到他
I bet his wife can't get a hold of him.
不错
Good point.
他被打动了 老板
He was impressed, boss.
不用担心 我们能搞定的
Don't worry, we got this.
我能让你们两个小情人呆一间里
I can get you two lovebirds a room.
我打赌你会喜欢的
I bet you'd like that.
来吧 你出去
Come on, get out of here.
我们有大人的事要讨论
We got grown man business to talk about.
如果斯特恩打来了我会告诉你的
I'll let you know if Stern calls.
就那么做
Do that.
看到那三人组了没?
You see the triads?
是啊 还有那些意大利人
Yeah, and the Italians.
没听到关于她的消息
Hadn't heard of her.
但是塞尔维亚人告诉我 你应该跟漂流谈谈
But the Serb told me you should talk to Drift.
我们不是要在搞定这一切之后
Aren't we supposed to meet with Drift
就去见漂流的吗?
as soon as we squash all this shit?
我觉得你们现在挺好的
I thought you two were cool, man.
是啊
Yeah.
你觉得如果他知道了什么他会有动作
You think he would've reached out if he knew something.
所以要么现在他什么也不知道
So either he doesn't know anything.
- 要么我们被耍了 - 是的
- Or we're getting played. - Yeah.
现在他妈还只有一个方法来搞清 汤米
And there's only one way to fucking find out, Tommy.
对 我们要去他那在
Yeah, we got to go visit him
泽西的见鬼的房子里见见他
in his fucked-up house in Jersey.
对啊
Mmm.
老兄 我讨厌那里
Man, I hate going out there.
你要开车的
You're driving.
来吧
Come on.
我不能和你一起去
I can't go with you, man.
我还有很多事要做
I got a lot to do for this party.
先留着
Save it.
听着 明天去 带上胡里奥
Look, go tomorrow. Take Julio.
我知道他今天拉肚子
I know he's doing runs today.
随便 老兄
Whatever, man.
安吉拉
Angela.
我们都在等你
We've been waiting for you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
很高兴再次看见你 柯林斯先生
It's good to see you again, Mr. Collins.
早上好
Good morning.
你觉得底特律怎么样?
How do you feel about Detroit?
我们正在那放置一个边界的毒品据点
We're putting together a border drug unit there,
需要借助一点你的才能
want someone of your caliber on board.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我没明白
I don't understand.
加利佛尼亚在洛沃斯那件事里
California appears to have made significant headway
取得了重要进展
in the Lobos case.
他的一个同伴被捕然后交代
An associate of his has been arrested and might sing.
如果他交代了 他们可能这周就要落网
If he does, they may be ready to arrest within the week.
他们正在停止我们在洛沃斯的任务
They're shutting down our Lobos task force.
我们正在转移资金到另一个部门
We're shifting funding to other departments.
我爸爸身体不太好
My father isn't in good health.
现在离开纽约不适合我
It's not a good time for me to leave New York.
弗兰基说你很有野心
Frankie said you were ambitious.
我以为你一定会抓住
I thought you'd jump at the chance
能成功起诉的机会
for a successful prosecution.
好吧 听着
All right, look.
除了在你的洛沃斯调查的巨大进展
Barring a huge development in your Lobos investigation,
我需要在本周结束前
I'm gonna need your answer about Detroit
得到你关于底特律的答案
by the end of the week.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
湿的么?
Is it wet?
真的?
It is?
噢 有多湿?
Oh, how wet?
呃 我要走了
Um, I got to go.
不用了
Don't even.
我了个去?
What the fuck?
他差不多就要杀了那个医生了
He was just about to kill the doctor.
痛
Ouch.
婊子 你疯了?
Bitch, are you crazy?
你会因为这个丢饭碗的
You could lose your job for this shit.
这就 像是 警察暴行
It's, like, police brutality.
我告诉过你的
I told you before.
没人在乎我对你做了什么
Nobody cares what I do to you.
我需要结果 诺马 现在
_
你还好吗 女巫婆?
You all right, bruja?
你肯定受刺激了
Something's got you shook.
跟我说说这本书
_
对我来说这些白人长得都一样
All these white boys look the same to me.
还有 这些混蛋都是小喽
Besides, these pendejos are small time.
你要找的那个王八蛋不在这里
The hijo de puta you're looking for ain't gonna be in here.
我告诉了你他的名字
I gave you his name.
- 你还要什么? - 他的照片
- What more do you want? - His picture.
你继续找 直到你找到他
So until you find him, you keep looking.
圣帕特里克夫人
Mrs. St. Patrick.
嘿 我很尽力赶到这了
Hey, I got here as quick as I could.
我告诉过你
I told you.
当我们单独相处时 你能叫我塔莎
When we're alone, you can call me Tasha.
你要我带你去哪里 塔莎?
So where do you need me to take you, Tasha?
- 随你定 - 什么?
- That's up to you. - What?
听着 我仔细想过你给我那些耳环时
Look, I've been thinking about what you said
说的话了
when you tried to give me those earrings,
关于幽灵 关于忠诚
about Ghost, about loyalty.
不不 我没什么其他意思
No, no, I didn't mean anything by it.
你当然是那个意思
Sure, you did.
你说得就像是
And the way you said it,
我丈夫在跟别的女人约会
seems like my husband is seeing another woman.
在我看来
And the way I see it,
如果他出轨了
if he's stepping out on our marriage...
或许我也应该这么做
Maybe I should, too.
听着 我知道你说那些
Look, I know you said what you said
是因为你关心我
because you care about me.
其实我也在乎你的
And I care about you too.
我是说 你不觉得比起被蒙在鼓里
I mean, don't you think I deserve better
我应该得到更好的吗?
than to be kept in the dark?
你去过底特律吗?
You ever been to Detroit?
去过几次 怎么了?
A couple times. Why?
你准备去?
You trying to go?
现在那里可不是个度假的好去处
Not exactly a vacation spot this time of year.
什么?
What?
不 不是去旅游
No, nothing like that.
你还好吗?
You okay?
怎么了?
What's up?
你觉得你这周还能出来 吃晚饭吗?
You think you can get out again this week, for dinner?
晚饭可能有点麻烦
Dinner time is tough,
因为孩子 你懂的
because of the kids, you know.
我知道
I know.
只是...
It's just...
我姐妹在我口袋里找到一些酒店的钥匙
My sister found some hotel keys in one of my pockets.
她问我怎么了 所以我...
She asked what was going on, so I...
你告诉了她
You told her.
关于我们
About us.
她想一起吃个晚饭 看看你怎么样
She wants to have dinner, see how you turned out.
帕斯怎么样了?
How is Paz?
她还在借钱吗?
Is she still borrowing money?
没有了
Never.
必须的
Exactly.
我还记得她敲碎了你的小猪储蓄罐
I remember her breaking your piggy bank,
然后她好去买她的糖
so she could buy some damn candies.
我想让她看看你变了多少
I want her to see how much you've changed.
那个晚餐在哪里 什么时候 我的女人?
When and where is this dinner, woman?
我会来的 我保证
I will be there, I promise.
后天?
Day after tomorrow?
你很幸运 我喜欢你
You're lucky I like you.
你确定要这么做?
You sure you want to do this?
我应该了解对手
I deserve to know what I'm up against.
那你要做什么?
What are you gonna do?
你觉得我会做什么?
What you think I'm gonna do?
不 那不是她
No, that's not her.
不是她
That's not her.
嗯
Hmm.
你知道她叫什么?
You know her name?
安吉拉
Angela.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
来这儿
Come here.
嘿
Hey.
我在俱乐部里见过她
I've seen her before, at the club.
幽灵跟她说话来着
Ghost was talking to her.
他说她只是高中朋友
He said it was just a friend from high school.
他跟我说... 他跟我说别烦恼
He told me... He told me not to trip.
我看见她 然后他...
I saw her, and he...
睡个好觉
have a good night.
直接带我回家
Just take me home.
听着 塔莎...
Look, Tasha...
拜托 带我回家
Just, please, take me home.
我们需要从头开始
We need to start over from the beginning.
想想阿尼巴尔
Consider Anibal.
泰诺人兄弟会有良好的社会关系
Hermanos Tainos are well-connected
而且有很大的势力范围
and have a lot of territory.
死了
Dead.
索尔达多族只是一个接头人
Soldado Nation's just as connected.
尽管洛沃斯让鲁伊斯滚开
And even though Lobos told Ruiz to fuck off,
他还是做了个尝试
he still made an attempt at the throne.
对他的惩罚是被小折刀割了喉咙
And his punishment was being aired out with a switchblade.
所以 阿尼巴尔死了
So Anibal is dead.
鲁伊斯排除了
Ruiz is out.
谁是下一个?
Who's next?
我们知道泰诺人兄弟会和索尔达多族
We know Hermanos Tainos and Soldado Nation
都在幽灵的网络里
are in Ghost's network.
所以我们要重游故地了
So we need to revisit the geo-profile
去寻找其他区的
to see what other crews in different boroughs
符合条件的帮派
fit the same criteria.
整个纽约有超过200个
There are over 200 criminal organizations
差不多符合条件的犯罪组织
in New York City that could apply.
筛选缩小范围要花上好几天
It could take us days to narrow that list.
我想你一定听到了他们的谈话
I'm sure you've heard the talk
关于要解散这个专案组
about breaking up this task force.
弗兰基和柯林斯脑子都进水了
Frankie and Collins are out of their fucking minds
他们觉得我连洛沃斯也没有找到
if they think I'm leaving this bitch
就空着手离开这个婊子
without getting Lobos.
我也这么想的
Me too.
死磕到底
Not until we're done.
这些伏都教的怪胎差点吓死我
This voodoo zombie shit freaks me the fuck out.
我暂且不去计较你的无礼
As you're unfamiliar with our religion,
鉴于你对我们的信仰还不是很熟悉
I will forgive your disrespect.
我很惊讶地听说你的...
I was surprised to hear about your...
麻烦事
Troubles.
你和幽灵经营了一个挺有名气的组织
You and Ghost run a respected network.
消息传播的真快
Word travels fast.
这让我不得不重新考虑我们之间的初次合作
It made me reconsider our fledgling partnership.
我们必须解决这件事
We'll get this handled.
只有你跟我说实话
We'll be back on track to do our thing,
我们的生意才能回归正轨
if you're straight with me.
我的堂兄们在迈阿密
I have cousins in Miami.
几年前 他们结识了
A few years ago, they crossed paths
一个西班牙女杀手
with a female Spanish hitter.
她很厉害
She was good,
镇压了帮派里的五个家伙
put down five people in his crew.
这个和你堂兄产生摩擦的帮派
Well, this crew that your cousins had a beef with,
你知道名字吗?
you got a name for me?
洛克街女杀手
Rock Street Killahz.
他们在弗罗里达有很大很大的势力
And they're very, very strong in Florida too.
你的朋友罗拉 他有一帮子当地的街头哥们
Your friend Rolla, he has street brothers there.
想要我给你出个价么?
Should I make an offering for you?
我想你需要它
I think you need it.
不用了 多谢
No, thanks.
等等 你要给幽灵打电话吗?
Hey, yo, you gonna call Ghost?
不
Nope.
不?
No?
伊莎贝尔 宝贝...
Isabela, mi amor...
你的饭一口没动
要我打你电话 来换回你的注意力么?
我只是有些担心你 你最近有些沉默寡言
不会是个男孩吧?
It's not a boy, is it?
显然不是 爸爸
It's definitely not a boy, papi.
头儿 有人找你
Jefe, you have a visitor.
你离开下
Hey.
我一点都不想看到你
I wasn't expecting you.
我也一点也不想来
I wasn't expecting to be here.
但是我这有急事需要告诉你
I got pressing business.
关于那个袭击我的婊子 我派人到处找寻
I got my crew on the streets, shaking trees.
但什么线索都没有
We got nothing on that bitch who hit me.
这正是我来说的
That's what I came to talk about.
我通过可靠途径得到了一条的消息
I got it on good authority
那个袭击我们又刺伤你的人
the people responsible for hitting us and stabbing you
可能是洛克街女杀手的
could be the RSK's.
你觉得可能吗?
Could that be?
索尔达多和洛克街女杀手
Soldados and RSK
一直不怎么对付
always had beef.
罗拉向来自大又固执
Rolla's arrogant, headstrong.
自从这事开始后 我就一直暗中监视着他
I had eyes on him since all of this started.
他正是能做出这种是的人
He's just the kind of man that makes a move like this,
面上看着很赞同你
looks you right in the face
背地里下手指指点点的家伙
and points the finger in the other direction.
问题是 幽灵会按照要求办事么?
The question is, will Ghost do what needs doing?
他会的
He'll do it.
我只需告诉他就行
I just need to talk to him.
难道他还不知道?
He doesn't know?
你先来找我了
You came to me first.
喔
Ooh.
我的兄弟 我们正处于十字路口上
We are at a crossroads, hermano,
这不仅仅关系到我们的事业
not just for everything we've worked for,
也关系到你自己
but for you.
应势而变很困难 但有时候却很必要
Change is hard and sometimes necessary.
或许这事你得自己来解决
Maybe you should handle this yourself.
不管怎样...
Either way...
那个婊子养的罗拉
必须干掉
Needs to be put into the dirt.
如果你不这样
And if you don't,
洛克街女杀手会继续每天都制造死亡
there's gonna be a body dropping from RSK every day.
可能是布朗克斯的三合会成员吗?
What about the triads in the Bronx?
他们实力小的不够看
Too small.
布鲁克林的那些俄罗斯人?
Russians in Brooklyn?
俄罗斯人会勾结拉丁美洲人?
Russians working with Latinos?
我很怀疑
I doubt it.
神探南茜 你一直不说话
Nancy Drew, you're quiet over there.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
皇后区的洛克街女杀手?
RSK in Queens?
为首的组织者叫做罗拉
The guy running the crew is named Rolla.
他有很严重的前科
He's got one serious rap sheet.
过去的半年里
RSK has doubled in scope and influence
洛克街女杀手加倍扩充了规模和影响力
over the last six months.
这说明了什么呢?
What can do that?
现金注入和新产品 都有可能
Influx of cash, new product, both.
明显是来自于洛沃斯
Lobos.
于是突然之间 洛克街女杀手的人控制了
Suddenly, the RSK's are controlling
一块非常大的领域
a huge amount of territory.
不管幽灵是谁 罗拉可以成为我们的切入点
Whoever Ghost is, Rolla could be our connect.
这绝对可行
It makes perfect sense.
但如果罗拉只是幽灵组织中的一员
If Rolla is in the Ghost network,
他要么是幽灵的下个目标
he's either Ghost's next target
要么至少知道幽灵是谁
or at least knows who he is.
但不管怎么说 我们都需要和他当面谈谈
Either way, we need to talk to him.
我们也许可以救他的命
We might just save his life.
我知道是谁跟踪我们了
I know who's been going after us.
是罗拉
Rolla.
漂流告诉你的吧
That's what Drift told you.
好吧 很好
Okay, all right.
让那些鬼扯见鬼去
Get the fuck out of here with that bullshit.
你一定是在和我开玩笑 对吧?
You're fucking with me, right?
几年前 漂流在迈阿密的表兄
Cousins of Drift's in Miami
被一个拉丁女杀手灭口了
were iced by a Latin girl hitter a few years back.
雇佣她的帮派来自洛克街女杀手的迈阿密据点
The crew that hired her was a Miami set of RSK's.
和罗拉有着直接的联系
Pretty straight line to Rolla from there.
汤米 你没有证据
That's not proof, Tommy.
鲁伊斯也这么认为
Ruiz thinks it is.
除非我们解决了这件事
He's threatened to go to war with the RSK's
不然他威胁说要跟洛克街女杀手开火了
unless we fix this.
首先 去他妈的鲁伊斯
First of all, fuck Ruiz.
我从来不会听从于他那样阴险的蠢货
I ain't never taken orders from his snake ass,
我现在也不会那样做
and I ain't gonna start now.
其次如果真的是罗拉 为什么他要那么做?
And secondly, why would Rolla do it?
我们认识他好多年了
We've known him for years.
你好好想想 我的伙计
Come on, man.
一样的原因 曾经的堂口男孩
Same reason two former corner boys
面对面地看着布雷兹
looked Breeze in the face
而后给他脑袋他妈的来了一下
and shot him in the fucking head.
当你想要上位的时候
When you want that top spot,
你会不惜一切代价来达成它
you're willing to do whatever it takes to get it.
我们所做过的的那些事
Everything we've been through,
是现在唯一说得通的
this is the only thing that makes sense now.
我告诉你 是罗拉干的
I'm telling you, it's Rolla.
我们必须在这上面达成一致 一半对一半
We're supposed to be partners in this shit, 50-50.
你是相信我的 对吧?
You trust me, right?
你和我都曾认为应该是阿尼巴尔
You and me were sure it was Anibal.
然后我们都确信应该是鲁伊斯干的
And then you and me were sure it was Ruiz.
你看 汤米 问题的关键是 我们不能再错了
See, Tommy, the problem is, we can't be wrong again.
我没有错
I'm not wrong.
这是现在最有可能的
This is the priority now.
不是他妈俱乐部 也不是任何其他的狗屁
Not this fucking club or any other bullshit
干扰我们正在做的事
that's been a distraction from what we're doing.
无论如何 这都会发生的
This is gonna happen, one way or another.
无论如何
One way or another.
如果你不想打仗
If you don't want a war,
那只有一种方法可以制止这样的结果
there's only one way to stop it.
我不会在没有证据的情况下开枪 汤米
I'm not pulling that trigger without proof, Tommy,
我办不到
no fucking way.
你不相信我 好
You don't believe me. Fine.
你要能找到 那你就去找他妈的证据吧
Get all the fucking proof you need, if you can,
一切截止到明天
by tomorrow.
杀死罗拉...
Kill Rolla...
或者我自己来
Or I will.
睡不着么 宝贝?
Can't sleep, baby?
抱歉 我不想吵醒你的
Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.
你在苦恼?
Something on your mind?
一直这样
Always.
也许你想谈谈它?
You want to talk about it?
塔莎 我有一个重大决定要做
I got a big decision to make, Tasha.
汤米怎么说?
What does Tommy think?
你是知道汤米的
You know Tommy.
他从不思考
He doesn't think.
他希望我相信他
He wants me to trust him, you know.
你要相信那些一直对你忠诚的人
You got to trust the people who've always been loyal to you.
汤米一直忠心耿耿
Tommy's always been loyal.
曾经是 现在可不一定了
Always has been, up until now.
那还有谁的判断是你可以相信的吗?
Is there anyone whose judgment you trust as much?
还有谁像这样一直支持着你吗?
Anyone who's been on your side all this time?
老J 我需要往北边送个包裹
Big J, I need to send a package upstate.
嘿 伙计 今晚熄灯时间是9点
Hey, yo, man, lights out is gonna be at 9:00 tonight.
什么都好 伙计
Whatever, man.
我什么时候关 那就什么时候熄灯
I turn them off when I turn them off.
你好吗 K?
What's up, K?
你这么急着联系我 那情况一定是很糟糕了
Must be real shit if you're reaching out this way.
该死 我从没这样一无所知 自从...
Shit, I ain't get no message like this since...
特伦顿斗殴
the Trenton Beef.
你曾经指引过我 好兄弟
Well, you guided me right then, man,
我现在要你注意打听
and I need your ear now.
你要干嘛?
So what you need?
看吧 伙计 我不知道你听说没有
Well, look, man, I don't know if you heard.
有人在打压我们的人
Someone's been hitting our crew,
到处丢下混账的东西
dropping motherfuckers left and right.
现在我听说洛克街女杀手可能有份参与
Now I heard rsk might be involved.
难以置信啊 你清楚吗?
Hard to believe, though, you know?
罗拉是个忠心的混蛋 伙计
Rolla a loyal motherfucker, man.
你一手成就了他
You made him what he is.
他不会跟我们对着干的
He wouldn't move against us.
是的 我也这么认为
Yeah, that's what I think.
可你知道不
But, you know,
我以前相信别人搞得现在焦头烂额
I trusted people before and been burned.
我听说了
I hear that.
好了 谈话结束
Well, word's out.
我今天得处理这破事儿
I got to move on this shit today,
不然就会有麻烦了 兄弟
or I got a war on my hands, bro.
不说了
Say no more.
保持联系 好吧?
Keep the phone close, all right?
好的 拜拜
All right. One.
我是詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
James St. Patrick here.
圣・帕特里克先生 我是西蒙・斯特恩
Mr. St. Patrick, this is Simon Stern.
你好
Oh, hello.
今晚六点你有空吗?
How does tonight work for you, 6:00 P.M.?
今晚六点不错
6:00 P.M. tonight is great.
好的
Good.
我会让我的助手给你地址
I'll have my assistant send you the address.
我期待很快见到你和你的妻子
I look forward to seeing you and your wife in a few hours.
还有别带那马屁精坎托斯
Oh, and leave that sycophantic boy wonder, Kantos,
在家 好吗?
at home, will you?
今晚只有成人
Tonight is adults only.
绝对地
Absolutely.
你看起来惊魂未定似的
You look like you just saw a ghost.
那是西蒙・斯特恩
That was Simon Stern.
今晚有晚宴
Dinner's tonight.
我跟你说什么了?
What did I tell you?
他想要合伙人
He wants to partner.
什么时候我们该到那?
What time should we be there?
不是你 今晚六点只有我和我妻子
Not you, just me and my wife at 6:00 P.M.
该死的 六点
Oh, shit, at 6:00.
我现在得打个电话
I got to go make a call, now.
玩得开心
Well, have a good time.
我猜
I guess.
几个鸡蛋?
两个
Dos.
感谢你帮我做这个
Thank you for doing this.
我想让你喜欢上他
I want you to like him.
他让我感到很幸福
He makes me happy.
我知道
I know.
你煮饭 这说明了很多
You cooking, it says a lot.
安琪 你怎么样了?
Angie, how you doing?
我全身都是面粉了
I'm covered in flour.
- 怎么了? - 斯特恩来电了
- What's up? - Stern called.
怎么样?
See?
无谓的担心
You were all worried for nothing.
没错 总是这样
You're right, always are.
他邀请我去他家吃晚饭
He invited me to dinner at their house.
安琪 是今晚
It's tonight, Angie.
我知道
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我会补偿你的
Look, I'll make it up to you.
我完事要回趟家
I need to swing by the house on my way back.
但过后我会路过你那
But I can come by after, you know.
没关系 别担心
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
今晚就专心去斯特恩那里吧
Focus on Stern tonight.
是吗?
Yeah?
是的 去做吧
Yeah. Go kill it.
好吧 谢谢
All right, thanks.
是要开会吗?
So it was a meeting?
所以他取消了晚餐?
That's why he cancelled?
是的 是个商务会议
A business meeting, yeah.
紧要关头就是生意
Pretty last-minute for a business thing,
你不这么认为吗?
don't you think?
没有 好了
Don't, okay.
我说说而已
I'm just saying,
难道对你来说这事听起来有点粗描淡写?
doesn't it sound a little sketchy to you?
我知道晚上到底会发生什么大事
I know what business happens last-minute at night,
并不是会议室那种事
and it ain't the kind in boardrooms.
如果他想让你开心
If he wants to make you happy,
他必须离开那混混的生活
he has to get off the streets.
我清楚你说的 他现在变了  安吉拉
I know you said that he's different now, Angela.
但对我来说都一样
帕斯 不是那样的
他结婚了
He's married.
他是个商人 真真正正的好人 正大光明
He's a businessman, legit, aboveboard, real.
我告诉你 从我们是孩子的时候他就变了
I told you, he's changed since we were kids.
他就是... 已婚了
He's just... Married.
旅馆钥匙
The hotel keys.
现在我懂了
Now I get it.
你应该是聪明的
And you're supposed to be the smart one.
你觉得能怎么样呢?
我爱他
我知道
I know.
我能看出来
I can tell.
可这不够
But it's not enough.
绝对不够
It never is.
从此以后不会幸福的
This isn't gonna be a happily ever after.
你看起来不错
You look great.
我希望你喜欢
Well, I'd hope you'd like it,
因为你为我选了所有好的东西
since you picked out everything for me to wear.
塔莎 今晚很重要
It's an important night, Tasha.
我们要上演好戏了 是吧?
We got to be on our A-game, all right?
我们要把握今晚 才能赢得明天
We got to handle tonight, so we earn a tomorrow.
别喝太猛了
So go easy on the drinking.
我不想这些人看到你喝醉
I don't need these people seeing you tipsy.
如果他妻子想闲聊
And if the wife wants to get chatty,
就加入吧
just play along with it.
我不会让你尴尬
I won't embarrass you.
好吧 幽灵?
Okay, Ghost?
我想这就是美丽的
Ah, I take it this is the lovely
圣・帕特里克太太
Mrs. St. Patrick.
詹姆斯没提过您是这么美
James didn't mention your beauty.
这是我的妻子 玛德琳
This is my wife, Madeline.
你好
Oh, hello.
你家真不错
Your home is beautiful.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
在博卡区那地儿感觉更像家
The place in Boca feels more like home,
可我们在这儿
but here we are.
斯特恩太太 幸会
Mrs. Stern, pleasure.
幸会
Likewise.
亲爱的 你带圣・帕特里克夫人参观一下吧?
Darling, why don't you take Mrs. St. Patrick on the tour?
詹姆斯和我有些事要谈
James and I have some business to talk about.
听我的 我们谈事儿的时候
Trust me, you do not want to be here
你不想在这的
when they talk about business.
你会睡着的
You will fall asleep.
我妻子很美 是吧?
My wife is beautiful, isn't she?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
预料之中的
It's expected, you know.
我们必须扮演那种人
We have to play the part.
他们必须看上去很像那种人
They have to look the part.
不久都会变得如此无聊
It all gets so goddamn boring after a while.
巴黎之花 1825产的
Ah, Perrier-Jouet, 1825.
不用了 谢谢
Oh, no thank you.
不喝酒的俱乐部老板
A club owner who doesn't drink.
真奇怪了
How curious.
你真让我吃惊 圣・帕特里克先生
You are full of surprises, Mr. St. Patrick.
我已经邀请另一对夫妇加入我们了
I've invited another couple to join us,
我助理和他妻子
one of my lieutenants and his wife.
托德和...
Todd and...
- 桑德拉 - 桑德拉
- Sandra. - Sandra.
这是詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
This is James St. Patrick.
-托德 桑德拉 - 幸会
- Todd, Sandra. - Pleasure.
我的荣幸
The pleasure's mine.
这是偷走月亮女神谢丹
This is the young upstart
聚会的新贵
who stole our Cynthia Sheridan parties.
就是我
That is me.
确是
It certainly is.
晚饭
Dinner.
吃饭了如何?
How about food?
开动吧
Let's eat.
格雷格:
罗拉没在最后已知的地点
还在查找
我要你半小时内来见我
I need you to meet me in 30 minutes.
然后他问"游艇要沉了?"
So then he asked, "do yachts like to sink?"
天啊 他们一走就好多了
Oh, God, it's so much better once they leave.
上帝知道他们不想和我们说话
God knows they don't want to talk to us.
我们也不想和他们说
And we do not want to talk to them.
亲爱的 真漂亮
Sweetie, those are so pretty.
是新的吗?
Are they new?
一万五美元
$15,000.
眼都没眨
Didn't bat an eye.
你应该至少从他那得到三十的股份
You should've got him for at least 30.
他们付钱的日子过去了
Price they pay for the time away.
对于那新俱乐部的位置本该有五十股份
Should've been 50 for that new club location
他经过额外调查了
he's been investigating on the side.
他们认为你不知道 这真是有趣
It's so funny how they think you don't know.
不 他们知道你已经知道了
Oh, no, they know you know.
他们就是不在乎
They just don't care.
嗯
Mm.
这才对了
That's the spirit.
唯一可以熬过这些事情的方法就是
The only way to get through these things
喝醉
is to stay drunk.
干杯
Cheers.
我可以问你些事吗?
Can I ask you something?
我可以摸摸你的头发吗?
Can I touch your hair?
我只是觉得太神奇了
I just think it's fascinating.
稍等一下
Excuse me for a second.
- 真漂亮 - 多可爱
- So pretty. - So cute.
小甜心
Darling.
当我还每天泡在夜店的时候
Back when I was still in the clubs day-to-day,
理想中的混血有模特 演员
the ideal mix was models, actors,
音乐家这类人
the musicians, of course,
政客们不希望落入法网
politicians hoping not to get caught,
同性恋 异装癖
gays, drag queens,
那些的光滑鲜嫩的年轻人
those smooth, hairless young men.
怎样都可以
Anything went.
自助餐的乐趣 美妙无穷
A buffet of pleasures, really.
艾滋病出现后 一切都被毁了
That was before aids came in and ruined everything.
我离题了
I digress.
我指的是 时代已经变了
My point is, times have changed.
如今在特定的元素中包含一个真正成功的混搭
A truly successful mix now involves a certain element
我承认我现在落伍了
a certain element that I admit I am less familiar with.
非裔美籍人和拉丁美洲人
African-Americans and Latinos
已经开始掌握真正的购买力
have begun to have real purchasing power.
他们正在市场上发号施令
They're dictating the marketplace,
而不仅是产生影响
not just influencing it.
你是怎么让黑人和拉丁人
How do you get the blacks and the Latins
夜夜出现 还举止端正的?
to show up night after night and behave?
他们和夜店的孩子们和社交名流混在一起
Mixing with the club kids and the socialites.
最重要的是 和辛西娅・谢里丹做生意
And on top of that, take my Cynthia Sheridan business.
有你这种背景的家伙通常在城外
Guys with your background usually open clubs uptown
或者在布鲁克林开夜店
or in Brooklyn
一个礼拜准关门 而你却没有
and open and close within a week, but not you.
你有什么秘密?
What's your secret?
不需要很详细 只说你的理念
No details, just your philosophy.
没有秘密 只因是我
There is no secret, just me.
我不明白
I don't follow.
我是混黑道的黑人
Well, I'm a black man from the hood.
我身边的家伙不是死就是进监狱
Most of the guys I came up with are either dead or in jail.
我住在阁楼
I live in the penthouse of my building,
楼下是律师和医生
above the lawyers and doctors
他们试图进我的夜店
trying to get into my club.
你看 人们会根据你西蒙的外表做判断
See, people take you at face value, Simon.
而我 则必须不断改变
Me, well, I have to transform
以满足每个人的期望
to meet everyone's expectations constantly.
真理夜店非普通之物 因为我也不是平庸之辈
Truth isn't one thing, because I'm not one thing.
明白了吗?
You understand?
我会使用我所有的经验
I take all my experiences and use them
来应对身处同一屋檐下不同类型的人
to cater to all different kinds of people, under one roof.
不论是专业的黑人运动员
Whether it's the black professional athlete,
点第二瓶伏特加
ordering his next bottle of Ciroc,
还是华尔街的混账
or whether it's the wall street motherfucker
用公费喝醉到失去意识
getting blackout drunk on the company's dime,
我理解他
I understand him.
我懂他
I get him.
而因为我了解他... 我就能拿下他
And because I get him...I get him.
因为我拿下他 我赚了钱
And because I get him, I get rich.
好吧 我想听具体的
Okay, I want to hear details.
我想要你出个价
I want your offer.
六百万美元
$6 million dollars.
开下一个夜店?
To open the next club?
不 是要完全拥有它
No, to own it outright,
把它归入我的名下
to add it to my brand.
真理不是用来出售的 西蒙
Truth is not for sale, Simon.
詹姆斯 你一旦开始
James, once you get started,
就没有时间寻找真理了
you won't even have time for Truth.
你会看到世界如此多人
You're gonna be seeing so much of this world,
在为我工作
working for me.
一切有关夜店的事情你都会忘记
You're gonna forget all about that club.
为你工作?
Working for you?
做我培训部的主管
As one of my executives in training.
我会教你经营之道
I'll bring you into management.
也许你会取代托德成为我的得力干将
Maybe you'll replace Todd here as my right hand.
有可能
Maybe.
我告诉你 我是成功真正的"秘密"
I told you, I'm "the secret" to Truth's success.
我不需要培训怎样成为我自己
I don't need training to be myself.
我来这 是来找生意伙伴的
I came here to discuss a partnership.
和你合作?
Partnership with you?
不行
No.
你也许有天分 但你还没准备好
You may be talented, but you're not ready.
但既然你这么特别
But since you are so unique,
来吧
you come on,
你可以直接向我汇报
I'll let you report directly to me.
我丈夫从不向任何人汇报
My husband doesn't report to anyone.
哦
Oh.
你是这么想的吗 詹姆斯?
Is that how you feel, James?
西蒙 我从不跟在别人后面
Simon, I didn't get where I am by following.
我走在前面
I lead.
我希望你能重新考虑合伙人的建议
I urge you to reconsider partnership,
因为如果我走出这个门
because if I walk out of that door,
我就从你的伙伴变回对手
I turn from potential ally back to competitor,
你不希望那样吧
and I don't think you want that.
我也不希望那样
I don't think you want that, either.
我会抓住机会的
I'll take my chances.
谢谢款待
Thank you for your hospitality.
希望最优秀的人笑到最后
May the best man win.
我会的
I will.
托德
Todd.
圣・帕特里克夫人 您很有胆色
Mrs. St. Patrick, you're a feisty one.
我很喜欢
I like that.
别担心 宝贝
Don't worry, baby.
你做的对
You did the right thing.
你不应该出来为我说话的 塔莎
It wasn't your call to speak for me, Tasha.
这是我自己做的决定
It's my decision to make.
根本没有什么决定
There was no decision.
你根本不是别人的二把手 对吗?
You're nobody's fucking number two, are you?
我的意思是 起初我就不明白
I mean, I don't even know why the hell we went up there
为什么我们要去那种鬼地方
in the first place.
你知道的 白人不想把你当成合作伙伴
You know that white man wasn't gonna see you as no partner.
该死的 你想让我怎样 塔莎?
The fuck you want from me, Tasha?
你想让我做什么?
What you want me to do?
你想让我保持现状 一成不变吗?
You want me to stay the same and never change?
你就没想过我已不是
It ever occur to you I ain't the same street nigger
你嫁的那个街头混混了
you married anymore?
谁打的?
Who's that?
卡南
Kanan.
哼
Hmph.
对我来说是同一个幽灵
Seems like the same old Ghost to me.
伙计 怎么了?
What's up, man?
我要说的话你不会喜欢的 幽灵
You ain't gonna like what I got to say, G.
关于罗拉 你是对的
You was right about Rolla.
这个小黑人拿出100美元
Little nigger put up 100 dollar
给任何能帮他与城外窝点
for anybody who could help link him
接头的人
with an out-of-town hitter.
他说他想当顶头老大
Said he wanted top of the line,
没错 为了破坏你整个联络网络
no mistakes, to take down your whole network.
十万美元
$100,000.
对 他们是这么说的
Yeah, that's what they're saying.
该死
Damn.
这儿的一些黑人得到来自迈阿密消息
Some of my niggers in here got connections down in Miami.
他们说罗拉一个月前到那儿旅行过
They said Rolla took a trip down there about a month ago,
他去那儿见他兄弟
met up with his brothers down there.
他们给他介绍给一个拉丁女孩
They introduced him to a Latin girl,
他们说女孩性感火辣 身边带着把刀
hot piece of ass they said knows her way around a knife.
婊子到哪儿都穿着骚粉的运动鞋
Bitch wear these crazy-ass pink sneakers everywhere she goes,
伙计 她们连上床都不脱掉
don't even take them off to fuck, man.
我们要找的就是这个妞 伙计
That's the chick we've been looking for, man.
罗拉 知道他有麻烦
Rolla know he in trouble,
所以他已经离开去了别的地方
so he already moving around a little different.
他正躲在长岛 婊子们的区域
He's hiding out on Long Island, some bitch's place.
我知道具体在哪
I know exactly where it is.
听着 K 小心点
Look, k, good looking out, man.
抬起头 好吗?
Keep your head up, all right?
好的
All right.
对不起 事情变成这样 幽灵
I'm sorry it turned out like this, G.
拜拜
One.
肖恩 你把塔莎送回家
Shawn, I need you to take Tasha home.
我要下车
I got to make a stop.
我说了 三十分钟 诺马
I said 30 minutes, Nomar.
迫不及待了 嗯?
Couldn't wait, huh?
我正在想 我不在你有没有孤单
I'm beginning to think you get lonely without me.
这是谁?
Who's this?
你认识他?
罗拉 是洛克街混蛋们的老板
Rolla, boss of the Rock Street Assholes.
他跟洛沃斯有关系吗?
Is he involved with Lobos?
就没有可能他的手下的人当中
There's no way he's got a blanquito in his crew
有追随幽灵的吗?
who might go by Ghost?
没有
No.
洛克街女杀手没有白人
No white guys in the RSK's.
至于洛沃斯 我知道罗拉认识鲁伊斯
As for Lobos, I know Rolla has history with Ruiz,
很长时间了
long-standing shit.
但我们被严格指示
But we're under strict instructions
如果在街上相遇 不要跟他们起冲突
not to mess with the RSK's if we see them on the streets.
像那种职业礼节?
Like a professional courtesy?
不能在联络网上和其他毒贩树敌?
Don't antagonize the other dealers in the network?
我不知道还有什么原因 让鲁伊斯阻止我们
I can't see another reason why Ruiz would keep us
把这些家伙踹出去
from stomping these motherfuckers out.
我到哪儿去找这个家伙?
Where can I find this guy?
我们去了最后他可能在的地方 他不在那儿
We went to his last known, and he wasn't there.
我能找到他
I can find out where he is.
他让雨披帮他监视每个他看不顺眼的人
He's got Poncho keeping tabs on everybody he's pissed at,
只是以防万一
just in case.
我给雨披打电话
I'll call him.
别问太多
Don't ask too much.
我不会的
I won't.
谢谢 诺马
Gracias, Nomar.
美女
你知道该怎样真诚感谢我吧?
打电话吧
Make the call.
打我手机
Try calling my cell.
什么?
What?
打我电话
Call my cell.
你吓到我了 汤米
You're scaring me, Tommy.
发生什么了
What's going on?
你可以告诉我的
You can tell me.
詹姆斯今晚本应该
James was supposed to
帮我做件事的
do something for me tonight.
狗娘养的最好今晚给我办好
Son of a bitch better do it tonight.
你觉得他会做吗?
Do you think he's gonna do it?
不会
No.
以前我们做什么都在一起
We used to do everything together,
并肩作战
side-by-side.
但现在变了
Something's changed.
他不再和以前一样了
He ain't the same.
你有想过你不再需要他了吗
You ever think you don't need him anymore?
如果你不相信让他来做今晚这事
I mean, if you don't trust him to do this thing tonight...
如果我不能相信他?
if I can't trust him?
那我也不知道了
Then I don't know.
我他妈不知道了
I don't fucking know.
如果你不能相信他 宝贝 你可以相信我
If you can't trust him, baby, you can trust me.
过来
Come here.
等你给我买回来吃的
As soon as you get back with my food,
我就让你过足瘾
I'll put this long nine on you.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Yeah? - Mm-hmm.
最好快点弄点吃的给我
Better hurry up with my food, yo.
我会请你喝一杯
I'd offer you a drink,
但我们都知道你不喝酒
but we both know you won't take it.
他们说今晚雪会下到十英尺深
They say we're gonna get ten inches tonight.
他们这样说吗?
That what they say, huh?
好吧 那我们最好开始行动了
Well, then we should probably get to it then.
你不想知道为什么吗
You don't want to know why?
我们都到这儿了
We here now.
知道为什么又有什么意思
Knowing why ain't gonna make no nevermind.
我知道一直都是你从内部攻击我们 罗拉
I know it's been you hitting us from the inside, Rolla,
这整段时间都在假惺惺对我笑
smiling in my face the whole fucking time, man.
你说那些屁话就像你真的相信一样
You actually said that shit like you truly believe it.
我真的相信
I do.
不 你不信
No, you don't.
因为如果你相信 我的黑屁股
'Cause if you did, my black ass
根本没机会坐下来
wouldn't even got a chance to sit down.
我是在给你一个澄清的机会
I'm offering you a chance to come clean.
不 不是
No, that ain't it.
你是在给我一个说服你的机会
You're offering me a chance to convince you.
好吧 听你的
Okay, I'll play along.
所以你的意思是我偷袭了你的货物
So you're saying I hit your shipment.
杀了胖子阿尼巴尔
I killed fat ass Anibal.
捅了鲁伊斯
I stabbed Ruiz.
我还干了什么
And what else I do?
几个星期之前
A few weeks ago,
你迫使我的一个送货员跳楼了 一个女人
you had a courier of mine jumped, a woman.
该死
Oh, damn.
原来我那么忙啊
I've been a busy motherfucker.
我们知道你雇佣的那个杀手
And we know about the hitter you hired,
一个拉丁裔女人
a female, Latina.
一个婊子?
A bitch?
我?
Me?
这太荒诞了 幽灵
That's a tall tale, G.
别耍我 孩子
Don't fuck with me, boy.
鲁伊斯已经决心要挑起战争了
Ruiz is down to go to war.
汤米也已经确信了
Tommy is convinced.
你别想耍我
Don't fuck with me.
听说你通过你迈阿密的兄弟们
Heard you went through your brothers in Miami
雇佣的这姑娘
to hire the chick.
是的 我的确去了迈阿密
Yeah, I went to Miami, sure,
晒的一身古铜色
and got a goddamn tan.
我可没雇穿裙子的杀手
I didn't get no hitter in a skirt.
像一个男人一样看着我的眼睛
Look me in the eyes like a man.
告诉我是你做的
Tell me you did it.
快承认把
Just own the shit.
我做不到 长官
I can't do it, Captain.
我懂鲁伊斯
I get Ruiz.
对 他如果去了西天
Yeah, his bitch ass go bye-bye,
我肯定会占了他的地盘 毋庸置疑
I'm gonna be on them corners, no doubt.
还有艾米纳姆 妈的
And Eminem, well, shit,
罗拉给汤米的外号
我们都知道他从来没喜欢过我
we both know he ain't never liked me.
但不是他们让你杀一个
But neither of them bring you to shooting a boy
你从小养大的孩子的 是吗
you raised from the streets, do they?
是卡南吧
It's Kanan, right?
你和那该死的疯子过了那么多年
You and that crazy motherfucker
还是关系很铁
still tight after all these years.
你比谁都相信他 甚至汤米
Shit, you trust him more than anybody, even Tommy.
问题是 幽灵
The question is, G,
他把你往我这方向指 他能得到些什么
what the fuck do he gain from pointing you in my direction?
他什么都得不到
He don't gain a motherfucking anything.
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend.
I am your friend.
据说今晚雪要下到十英尺是吗?
Said we're supposed to get ten inches tonight, huh?
尸体还是暖的
Still pretty warm.
- 去你的 - 是啊
- Carajo. - Yeah.
我要叫警察了
I'll call NYPD.
可能杀手还在这附近
Maybe the killer's still in the area.
谢了 姑娘
Thanks, girl.
所以他终究还不是你的白马王子
So he wasn't prince charming after all.
除非王子是个脚踏两只船的黑人
Unless princey was a two-timing nigger.
你有和他个没用的家伙对峙过吗
Have you confronted his worthless ass?
凯莎 你别...
Keisha, you don't...
是他娶你的
he's the one who married you,
在每张账单上写你的名字 每张纸上
put your name on every bill, on every paper.
你有他的孩子 漂亮的豪华公寓
You have his kids, this fancy penthouse,
还有他的银行账户
his bank accounts.
全拿走吧 T
Take it all, "T."
跟这混蛋离婚
Divorce his ass
把他所有的财产都拿走
and take every last bit of it.
那小三不是白人吧?
She ain't white, is she?
因为我能理解幽灵这样一个人走那条路
'Cause I could see a brother like Ghost going that way.
不 她不是白人
No, she ain't white.
也不是黑人
Ain't black, either.
跟我完全不一样
Nothing like me at all.
对于你正经历的事我很抱歉 T
Sorry you're going through this, "T."
但你得照顾好自己
But you got to take care of yourself.
幽灵丢掉了他的忠诚
Ghost took back his loyalty.
所以现在是时候你做一样的事了
So now it's time for you to do the same.
英雄万岁
All hail the goddamn conquering hero.
这红头发的现在住在这里了吗
The redhead lives here now?
不用担心她
Don't worry about her.
她无关痛痒
She's out cold.
现在能把我们的朋友从圣诞名单中划掉了吗
So can we scratch our friend off the Christmas list?
你做了该做的事 幽灵
You did what needed to be done, G.
我要回家 伙计
I'm going home, man.
这是为了以后的好日子 兄弟
It's a good day's work, brother.
是啊
Yeah.
你来这儿多久了?
How long have you been here?
我应该回家了
I was supposed to go home.
事实上 我家已经没有家的感觉了
The truth is, my place doesn't feel much like home anymore.
抱歉我放你鸽子了
Sorry I stood you up.
斯特恩怎么样了
How was Stern's?
你应该带你去的
I should've taken you.
别这么说
Don't say that.
我们没有在约会
We're not dating.
我们也不是情侣
We're not a couple.
我们只是两个愚蠢的孩子玩着过家家
We're just two stupid kids playing house,
努力拥抱一个幻境
trying to wrap our hands around a fantasy.
我很想念那个晚上 安琪
I missed one night, Angie.
你想念每一个夜晚
You miss every night.
我需要你听我说完
I need you to hear me.
我想要为你改变我的生活
I want to change my life for you.
我不想毁了你的婚姻
I don't want to break up your marriage.
我从来都不是这种人
That's not the person I ever thought I would be.
这件事责任在你了 杰米
So this is on you now, Jamie.
如果你是在告诉我这事 我们 会梦想成真
If you are telling me that this, us, is gonna happen,
那就必须成真
then it has to happen,
因为如果你没办成
because I don't know what I'm gonna do
我不知道我该怎么办
if you don't come through.
我会办成的
I'll make it happen.
说你爱我就好
Just say you love me.
杰米
Jamie.
说啊
Say it.
我爱你 好了吧?
I love you, okay?
罗拉死了
Rolla's dead.
幽灵 你个蠢货
Ghost, you dumb motherfucker.
有人知道是他做的吗
Anybody know he did it?
还没有
Not yet.
我们知道两件事
Well, we know two things.
第一 幽灵信任我
One, Ghost trusts me.
第二 他现在孤身一人了
And two, he's all alone now,
刚抓住汤米
just got Tommy.
那孩子太蠢看不出接下来的事
And that boy way too dumb to see what's coming.
你搞糟了 鲁伊斯活下来了
It's so much better that you fucked up,
这好多了
and Ruiz lived.
当我打电话的时候
He gonna come looking for protection
他会寻求保护
when I come calling.
你欠我钱
You owe me money.
十万
100K.
你还欠我几条人命呢
And you owe me bodies.
但我会给你别的机会来弥补
But I'm gonna give you another chance to get it done.
我会付全款的
I'll pay full freight.
还有宝贝 你得买双新鞋了
Oh, and, honey, you're gonna need to get you some new shoes.
听着
Look.
你要确保当你动手的时候
You make sure my son ain't there
我儿子不在场 好吗
when you do it, neither, right?
好的
Right.
- 什么时候 - 我会给你信号的
- When? - I'll give you the signal.
我要幽灵死 在我出狱之前
I want Ghost dead before I get out.